pornado.co 2018-09-03

# 

**Pornado.co Privacy Policy**

**Created: July 10, 2015**

**Last Updated: July 10, 2015**

DH Digital Services, Inc. respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy. This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website [pornado.co](http://pornado.co/) (“ _ **Website**_ ”) and our practices for collecting, using, keeping, protecting, and disclosing that information. 

This policy applies to information we collect:

  * On this Website (including desktop and mobile versions).

  * In email, text, and other electronic messages between you and this Website.

  * When you interact with our advertising on third-party websites and services, if the advertising include links to this policy.

  * When you interact with this Website through third-party social media platforms.

It does not apply to information collected by:

  * us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by DH Digital Services or any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries); or

  * any third party (including our affiliates and subsidiaries), including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from (or on) the Website.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices about your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change on one or more occasions. We will consider your continued use of the Website after we make changes as your acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy frequently for updates. 

  1. **Are minors welcome on our Website?**

We do not intend this Website for minors. The Website limits access to adults’ at least 18-years old that have reached the age of majority in their jurisdiction. We prohibit all persons who do not meet the age requirements from accessing this Website. We do not knowingly collect any personal information from or about minors, and minors may not access this Website or use its services.

Under 47 U.S.C. § 230(d), we notify you that parental control protections (including computer hardware, software, or filtering services) are commercially available that may assist in limiting access to material that is harmful to minors. You may find information about providers of these protections on the Internet by searching “parental control protection” or similar terms. If minors have access to your computer, please restrain their access to sexually explicit material by using any of the following products provided for informational purposes only and not endorsed by us: [CYBERsitter™](http://www.cybersitter.com/) | [Net Nanny®](http://www.netnanny.com/) | [CyberPatrol](http://www.cyberpatrol.com/) | [ASACP](http://www.asacp.org/).

  2. **What types of information do we collect about you?**

_**Information we collect from users**_

The Website is a free service for surfers that does not require registration or the submission of any personal information to use the Website. We offer free registration to the Website; registration is required to upload content. If you decide to register, we only collect your email address. 

You also may provide information to be published or displayed on public areas of the Website, or transmitted to other users of the Website or third parties. Your user contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Website with whom you may choose to share your user contributions. Thus, we cannot and do not guarantee that your user contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

_**Information we collect through social media**_

We may allow you to engage with the Website’s content and other offerings on or through third-party social media websites, like Facebook® and Twitter®. If we do, when you link your account or engage with content on or through third-party social media websites, services, plugins, or applications, you may allow us to have ongoing access to certain information from your social media account. We may also receive nonpersonally identifiable information from your interaction with the Website’s content, including content viewed, content preferences, and information about any advertisements within the content you have been shown or may have clicked on. 

When you provide information to the Website from your social media account, it can help enable us to do things like: (1) give you exclusive content; (2) personalize your online experience with us within and outside this Website; and (3) contact you through the social media websites or directly with the latest news, special offerings, and rewards. By providing this information, you consent to the use of the information according to this privacy policy.

If you interact with this Website through social media websites, plugins, or other applications, then, depending on your privacy settings, this information may become public on the Internet. You acknowledge that we cannot prevent further use of this information once it becomes public on the Internet. You can control what data you share through privacy settings available on some social media websites. For more information about how you can customize your privacy settings and how third-party social media websites handle your personally identifiable information, please refer to their privacy help guides, privacy policies, and terms. 

_**Information we collect about usage**_ ****

We collect certain nonpersonally identifiable information when you access the Website. For example, we may collect information on the type of browser you are using, the type of operating system you are using, the domain name of your Internet service provider, IP address, and certain usage information including the locations of the webpages that you viewed right before arriving at, while navigating, and immediately after leaving the Website, and the convent viewed while accessing the Website (including any up votes and down votes).

_**Information we collect from mobile devices**_

If you access this Website through a mobile device (e.g., smartphone, tablet, etc.), we may collect your unique device identifier and mobile device IP address, as well as information about your mobile device’s operating system, mobile carrier, mobile Internet browsers, your precise geographic location information, and other information described in this privacy policy. If you do not want your location known, you can turn off location services on your mobile device by going to “(1) settings, (2) location services, (3) off” for iOS devices; and “(1) profile, (2) privacy, (3) on” for Android devices.

_**Information we collect from other sources**_

On one or more occasions, we may combine information we receive online with outside records and use the information according to this privacy policy. We will combine information in a way that does not personally identify you.

  3. **How do we collect information about you?**

We collect information about you:

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us.

  * Automatically as you navigate through the Website. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies (including login details and voting and viewing history). We do not collect personal information automatically. 

The information we collect automatically is statistical data and does not include personal information, but we may keep it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by allowing us to:

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.

  * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.

  * Speed up your searches.

  * Recognize you when you return to our Website.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

  * _**Cookies (or browser cookies)**_. _ ****_ A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. Information gathered through cookies may include date and time of visit, webpages viewed, time spent at our Website, and the websites visited just before and just after our Website. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. But if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website. If you want to learn more about cookies, please see [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). 

  * _**Web Beacons**_. Pages of our Website (and our emails) may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit DH Digital Services, for example, to count users who have visited those pages (or opened an email) and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity). If you want to learn more about web beacons, please see [www.allaboutcookies.org/web-beacons/](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/web-beacons/). 

  4. **How do we use your information?**

We may use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

  * To present our Website and its contents to you.

  * To suggest and recommend relevant content based on your viewing or voting history. 

  * To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.

  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.

  * To provide you with notices about your account.

  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.

  * To notify you about changes to our Website, Website news or announcements, special offers, or any products or services we offer or provide through the Website.

  * To allow you to participate in any interactive features on our Website (including the voting system).

  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.

  * For any other purpose with your consent.

  5. **With whom do we share your information?**

We may disclose aggregated information about you, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

  * To our subsidiaries and affiliates.

  * To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business.

  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of DH Digital Services’ assets, whether as a going concerning or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by DH Digital Services about our Website users is among the assets transferred.

  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.

  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.

  * With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.

  * To enforce or apply our terms of use

  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of DH Digital Services, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and prevention.

  6. **What choices do you have about how we use and disclose your information?**

We strive to provide you with choices about the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

  * _**Tracking technologies**_. You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this Website may then be inaccessible or not function properly. To learn how to manage cookies, please see [www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/).

  * _**Marketing communications.**_ At this time, we do not intend to send users advertising or marketing materials. If we do in the future, you can opt-out by (1) following the “unsubscribe” instructions in any marketing email you receive from us or (2) sending us an email at [contact@pornado.co](mailto:contact@pornado.co) to request removal from future email distributions. This opt-out does not apply to transactional emails, including service announcements and administrative notices.

  7. **How do you access and correct your information?**

You may send us an email at [contact@pornado.co](mailto:contact@pornado.co) to request access to, correct, or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We will not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect. 

  8. **How do we protect your personal information?**

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, change, and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls. 

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information over the Internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Website. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website.

  9. **Does this privacy policy apply to third-party links?**

We provide links to third-party websites for your convenience. Once you leave our digital environment, we are no longer responsible for and cannot control what is collected on these websites. Please see the website’s relevant privacy policy for how that website handles your information.

  10. **Do we comply with Do Not Track?**

Do Not Track (“DNT”) is a privacy preference that you can set in your browser. DNT is a way for you to inform websites and services that you do not want certain information about your webpage visits collected over time and across websites or online services. We are committed to providing you with meaningful choices about the information we collect and that is why we provide you the ability to opt-out. But we do not recognize or respond to any DNT signals as the Internet industry works toward defining exactly what DNT means, what it means to comply with DNT, and a common approach to responding to DNT. For more information about DNT signals, you may visit [www.allaboutdnt.com](http://www.allaboutdnt.com/). 

  11. **Where do we process EU personal information?**

Any personal information collected about EU visitors through the services is processed in the United States or in other countries in which we or our affiliates, subsidiaries, or service providers host these services. When you provide personal information to us through the services, you consent to the processing of your data in, and the transfer of your data to, the United States or any other country in which we or our affiliates, subsidiaries, or service providers host these services.

  12. **Your California Privacy Rights**

If you are a California resident, you have the right to receive (1) information identifying any third-party company to whom we may have disclosed, within the past calendar year, personal information concerning you and your family for our direct marketing purposes; and (2) a description of the categories of personal information disclosed. If you want to exercise this right, you must make a request in writing to us to obtain this information. We will not process your request unless it includes your full name, email address, postal address, the URL for the website you visited, and the subject line labeled “Your California Privacy Rights.” Please email your request to [legal@pornado.co](mailto:legal@pornado.co). We will only honor one request per calendar year. 

  13. **DMCA take-down requests**

This Website complies with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act. If you reasonably believe your copyrighted work has been used or posted by a third party without your consent, you may follow the instructions here on how to report it. 

By submitting a copyright infringement notice or other communication (including communications about content stored on or transmitted through the Website), you consent to have these communications forwarded to the person or entity who stored, transmitted, or linked to the content addressed by your communication, in order to facilitate a prompt resolution. We forward DMCA infringement notices (including any personally identifying information contained in the notices) as submitted to us without any deletions.

  14. **Changes to Privacy Policy**

We post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat your personal information, we will notify you by email to the email address specified in your account (if you are a webmaster) or through a notice on the Website home page. The privacy policy identifies when we last updated it at the top of the page. You are responsible for making sure we have an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you (if you are a webmaster), and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes. 

  15. **Contact Information**

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at [legal@pornado.co](mailto:legal@pornado.co). 

This document prepared by [_Walters Law Group_](http://www.firstamendment.com/). © 2015. All rights reserved.
